var questions = [{
	"question": "Programmer who works with high level languages and have better understanding with applications are considered as ?",
	"option1": "Design programmer",
	"option2": "Application programmer",
	"option3": "Analysis programmer",
	"option4": "Train programmer",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "Programmer who works with high level languages and have better understanding with applications are considered as ?",
	"option1": "Terminal control staff",
	"option2": "Data control staff",
	"option3": "Peripheral control staff",
	"option4": "Librarian control staff",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "Which is a single integrated circuit?",
	"option1": "Gate",
	"option2": "Mother Board",
	"option3": "Chip",
	"option4": "CPU",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "C is ?",
	"option1": "A third generation high level language",
	"option2": "A machine language",
	"option3": "An assembly language",
	"option4": "All of the above",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "Web pages are written using ?",
	"option1": "FTP",
	"option2": "HTTP",
	"option3": "HTML",
	"option4": "URL",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "UNIVAC is an example of",
	"option1": "First generation computer",
	"option2": "Second generation computer",
	"option3": "Third generation computer",
	"option4": "Fourth generation computer",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "Which of the following is an example of non volatile memory ?",
	"option1": "VLSI",
	"option2": "LSI",
	"option3": "ROM",
	"option4": "RAM",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Graphic interfaces were first used in a xerox product is called ?",
	"option1": "Ethernet",
	"option2": "Inter LISP",
	"option3": "Small talk",
	"option4": "Zeta LISP",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "Find the odd one out ?",
	"option1": "ORACLE",
	"option2": "SYBASE",
	"option3": "C",
	"option4": "INFORMIX",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Person who keeps disc and tape files up to date for computer installation is called",
	"option1": "File librarian",
	"option2": "Punch librarian",
	"option3": "Peripheral librarian",
	"option4": "Termianl librarian",
	"answer": "1"
}];